<resources>
    <array name="movie_poster">
        <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_glass</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hunterkiller</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_marrypopins</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_mortalengine</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_preman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_robinhood</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_spiderman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_thegirl</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_themule</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>
    </array>
    <array name="movie_title">
        <item>A Star is Born</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Avengers Infinity War</item>
        <item>BirdBox</item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>BumbleBee</item>
        <item>Creed II</item>
        <item>DeadPool 2</item>
        <item>How To Train Your Dragon The Hidden World</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball Broly The Movie</item>
        <item>Glass</item>
        <item>Hunter Killer</item>
        <item>Marry Poppins Returns</item>
        <item>Mortal Engines</item>
        <item>Preman Pensiun</item>
        <item>Robin Hood</item>
        <item>SpiderMan: Into The Spider Verse</item>
        <item>The Girl In The Spider\'s Web</item>
        <item>The Mule</item>
        <item>Venom</item>
    </array>
    <array name="movie_ph">
        <item>Warner Bros. Pictures</item>
        <item>DC Entertainment</item>
        <item>Marvel Studios</item>
        <item>Netflix</item>
        <item>GK Films</item>
        <item>Hasbro</item>
        <item>MGM Pictures, Warner Bros</item>
        <item>20th Century Fox, Marvel</item>
        <item>DreamWorks</item>
        <item>Toei, Fox International</item>
        <item>Universal Pictures</item>
        <item>HK Productions</item>
        <item>Walt Disney</item>
        <item>MRC</item>
        <item>MNC Pictures</item>
        <item>Summit Entertainment</item>
        <item>Sony, Columbia Pictures, Marvel</item>
        <item>Columbia Pictures, MGM</item>
        <item>Warner Bros</item>
        <item>Columbia, Marvel</item>
    </array>
    <array name="movie_storyline">
        <item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine (Bradley Cooper) discovers-and falls in love
            with-struggling artist Ally (Gaga). She has just about given up on her dream to make it
            big as a singer - until Jack coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Ally\'s career
            takes off, the personal side of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an
            ongoing battle with his own internal demons.
        </item>
        <item>Arthur Curry, half human half from Atlantis, goes on a trip of a lifetime. Not only
            does this adventure compel him to come to terms with his real identity, but it also
            forces him to discover whether he is entirely worthy of fulfilling his own destiny:
            becoming a king.
        </item>
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too
            large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows:
            Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity
            Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all
            of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment, the fate
            of Earth and existence has never been more uncertain.
        </item>
        <item>In the wake of an unknown global terror, a mother must find the strength to flee with
            her children down a treacherous river in search of safety. Due to unseen deadly forces,
            the perilous journey must be made blindly. Directed by Emmy winner Susanne Bier, Bird
            Box is a thriller starring Academy Award winner Sandra Bullock, John Malkovich, Sarah
            Paulson, and Trevante Rhodes.
        </item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody is a foot-stomping celebration of Queen, their music and their
            extraordinary lead singer Freddie Mercury. Freddie defied stereotypes and shattered
            convention to become one of the most beloved entertainers on the planet. The film traces
            the meteoric rise of the band through their iconic songs and revolutionary sound. They
            reach unparalleled success, but in an unexpected turn Freddie, surrounded by darker
            influences, shuns Queen in pursuit of his solo career. Having suffered greatly without
            the collaboration of Queen, Freddie manages to reunite with his bandmates just in time
            for Live Aid. While bravely facing a recent AIDS diagnosis, Freddie leads the band in
            one of the greatest performances in the history of rock music. Queen cements a legacy
            that continues to inspire outsiders, dreamers and music lovers to this day.
        </item>
        <item>On Cybertron, the Autobots, led by Optimus Prime, are on the verge of losing the Great
            Cybertronian War to their enemies, the Decepticons, and begin making preparations to
            leave the planet. The Decepticons led by Shockwave, Soundwave and Starscream ambush them
            during the evacuation, and Optimus sends a young scout, B-127, to Earth in order to set
            up a base of operations where the Autobots can regroup. B-127 reaches Earth alone in
            1987, crash-landing in California and disrupting a training exercise being conducted by
            Sector 7, a secret government agency that monitors extraterrestrial activity on Earth.
            Sector 7 agent Colonel Jack Burns presumes B-127 to be a hostile invader and attacks,
            driving B-127 into the forest, where he is then ambushed by the Decepticon Blitzwing.
            When B-127 refuses to reveal Optimus\' whereabouts, Blitzwing spitefully tears out his
            voice-box and damages his memory core. B-127 manages to destroy Blitzwing before
            collapsing from his wounds.
        </item>
        <item>Years after Adonis Creed made a name for himself under Rocky Balboa\'s mentorship, the
            young boxer becomes the Heavyweight Champion of the World. While life is good with that
            victory and his marriage to Bianca, trouble comes to Philadelphia when Ivan Drago, the
            Russian boxer who killed Adonis\' father, Apollo, arrives with his son, Viktor, to
            challenge Adonis. Against Rocky\'s advice, Adonis accepts the challenge without his
            mentor\'s participation and pays the price in a punishing bout he wins only by a
            technicality. Now injured and demoralized, Adonis cannot bring himself to back into the
            game, leaving his spirit and title in jeopardy. Together, Adonis\' family and Rocky must
            find a way to rekindle Adonis\' fighting spirit to face the future in whatever choice he
            makes. Meanwhile, the Drago family have its own troubles trying to regain the respect in
            their homeland that they lost at Rocky\'s hands as they wonder whether is it truly worth
            it.
        </item>
        <item>After losing Vanessa (Morena Baccarin), the love of his life, 4th-wall breaking
            mercenary Wade Wilson aka Deadpool (Ryan Reynolds) must assemble a team and protect a
            young, full-figured mutant Russell Collins aka Firefist (Julian Dennison) from Cable
            (Josh Brolin), a no-nonsense, dangerous cyborg from the future, and must also learn the
            most important lesson of all: to be part of a family again.
        </item>
        <item>As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless\'
            discovery of an untamed, elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at
            home and Hiccup\'s reign as village chief is tested, both dragon and rider must make
            impossible decisions to save their kind.
        </item>
        <item>Goku and Vegeta encounter Broly, a Saiyan warrior unlike any fighter they\'ve faced
            before.
        </item>
        <item>After pursuing Kevin Wendell Crumb and the multiple identities that reside within.
            David Dunn finds himself locked in a mental hospital alongside his archenemy, Elijah
            Price and must contend with a psychiatrist who is out to prove the trio do not actually
            possess superhuman abilities
        </item>
        <item>A U.S. submarine, the USS Tampa Bay, vanishes while shadowing a Russian Akula-class
            submarine in the Arctic. Rear Admiral John Fisk sends a Virginia-class submarine, the
            USS Arkansas, under the command of newly-promoted and unorthodox Commander Joe Glass to
            investigate. At the same time, a Navy SEAL team under the command of Lieutenant Bill
            Beaman is sent in to discreetly observe a Russian naval base. When they arrive at the
            naval base, they witness defense minister Dmitri Durov conducting a coup d\'etat and
            taking Russian President Zakarin prisoner, and swiftly realize that Durov intends to
            trigger a war.
        </item>
        <item>In Depression-era London, a now-grown Jane and Michael Banks, along with Michael\'s
            three children, are visited by the enigmatic Mary Poppins following a personal loss.
            Through her unique magical skills, and with the aid of her friend Jack, she helps the
            family rediscover the joy and wonder missing in their lives.
        </item>
        <item>A mysterious young woman, Hester Shaw, emerges as the only one who can stop a giant,
            predator city on wheels devouring everything in its path. Feral, and fiercely driven by
            the memory of her mother, Hester joins forces with Tom Natsworthy, an outcast from
            London, along with Anna Fang, a dangerous outlaw with a bounty on her head.
        </item>
        <item>After three years, the business of Muslihat, who has retired as a thug, has a problem.
            Sales decline. Muslihat also faces new problems when Safira, her only daughter, grows up
            in adolescence and begins to be visited by boys. A bigger problem: frictions between his
            former subordinates.
        </item>
        <item>A war-hardened crusader Robin of Loxley (Taron Egerton) and his Moorish commander
            (Jamie Foxx) mount an audacious revolt against the corrupt English crown.
        </item>
        <item>Miles Morales is a New York teen struggling with school, friends and, on top of that,
            being the new Spider-Man. When he comes across Peter Parker, the erstwhile saviour of
            New York, in the multiverse, Miles must train to become the new protector of his city.
        </item>
        <item>In Stockholm, Sweden, vigilante hacker Lisbeth Salander is hired by computer
            programmer Frans Balder to retrieve Firefall, a program capable of accessing the
            world\'s
            nuclear codes that he developed for the National Security Agency, as Balder believes it
            is too dangerous to exist. Lisbeth successfully retrieves Firefall from the NSA\'s
            servers, attracting the attention of agent Edwin Needham, but is unable to unlock it,
            and the program is later stolen from her by mercenaries led by Jan Holtser, who also
            attempt to kill Lisbeth. When she doesn\'t attend their scheduled rendezvous, Balder
            mistakenly believes Lisbeth decided to keep Firefall for herself and contacts Gabrielle
            Grane, the deputy director of the Swedish Security Service (Säpo), who moves Balder and
            his young son August to a safe-house. Meanwhile, Needham tracks the unauthorized login
            to Stockholm and arrives to seek Lisbeth and Firefall.
        </item>
        <item>Clint Eastwood stars as Earl Stone, a man in his 80s who is broke, alone, and facing
            foreclosure of his business when he is offered a job that simply requires him to drive.
            Easy enough, but, unbeknownst to Earl, he\'s just signed on as a drug courier for a
            Mexican cartel. He does well, so well, in fact, that his cargo increases exponentially,
            and Earl is assigned a handler. But he isn\'t the only one keeping tabs on Earl; the
            mysterious new drug mule has also hit the radar of hard-charging DEA agent Colin Bates.
            And even as his money problems become a thing of the past, Earl\'s past mistakes start
            to
            weigh heavily on him, and it\'s uncertain if he\'ll have time to right those wrongs
            before
            law enforcement, or the cartel\'s enforcers, catch up to him."
        </item>
        <item>After a faulty interview with the Life Foundation ruins his career, former reporter
            Eddie Brock\'s life is in pieces. Six months later, he comes across the Life Foundation
            again, and he comes into contact with an alien symbiote and becomes Venom, a parasitic
            antihero.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="movie_rating">
        <item>7,7</item>
        <item>7,1</item>
        <item>8,5</item>
        <item>6,6</item>
        <item>8,0</item>
        <item>6,8</item>
        <item>7,2</item>
        <item>7,7</item>
        <item>7,5</item>
        <item>7,9</item>
        <item>6,7</item>
        <item>6,6</item>
        <item>6,8</item>
        <item>6,1</item>
        <item>7,8</item>
        <item>5,3</item>
        <item>8,4</item>
        <item>6,1</item>
        <item>7,0</item>
        <item>6,7</item>
    </array>

    <string name="app_name">MooVie</string>

    <string name="title_movies">Mortal Engines</string>

    <string name="ph_movies">Warner Bros. Pictures</string>

    <string name="title_storyline">Storyline</string>

    <string name="lorem">On Cybertron, the Autobots, led by Optimus Prime, are on the verge of losing the Great
            Cybertronian War to their enemies, the Decepticons, and begin making preparations to
            leave the planet. The Decepticons led by Shockwave, Soundwave and Starscream ambush them
            during the evacuation, and Optimus sends a young scout, B-127, to Earth in order to set
            up a base of operations where the Autobots can regroup. B-127 reaches Earth alone in
            1987, crash-landing in California and disrupting a training exercise being conducted by
            Sector 7, a secret government agency that monitors extraterrestrial activity on Earth.
            Sector 7 agent Colonel Jack Burns presumes B-127 to be a hostile invader and attacks,
            driving B-127 into the forest, where he is then ambushed by the Decepticon Blitzwing.
            When B-127 refuses to reveal Optimus\' whereabouts, Blitzwing spitefully tears out his
            voice-box and damages his memory core. B-127 manages to destroy Blitzwing before
            collapsing from his wounds.</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="rating">5,7</string>
    <string name="movies_genre">Sci Fi, Thriller</string>
    <string name="title_movie_trailer">Movie Trailer</string>


</resources>
